Alladin Melico

Full Stack Developer

Portfolio: https://alladinmelico.github.io

+639560333490

melico.alladin@gmail.com

New Lower Bicutan, Taguig City PH

https://github.com/alladinmelico

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alladin-m

An award-winning full stack developer with over 3 years of experience specializing in Node.js, Laravel, React.js and Vue.js.

I have collaborated with various startups in Australia, demonstrating excellent written and oral communication skills (C2 Proficient). I am self-motivated and quickly adapt to new tools and technologies.

SKILLS

in

- JS Node.js, React.js, Vue.js,
 AlpineJS, Inertia.js
- PHP Laravel, Codelgniter, Livewire
- Typescript
- CSS Tailwind, SCSS, SASS
- UI Vuetify, MUI, Bootstrap, Lit.dev
- HTML, JSON
- Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB, NoSQL
- · REST API, GraphQL
- Git Github/Gitlab
- Cypress/Jest
- · AWS, DigitalOcean, Forge
- UI/UX Figma, Adobe XD, Balsamiq
- CMS Nova, Filament, Wordpress
- Jira, ClickUp, Trello

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Amaze Communication

Sydney, Australia

Dec 2023 - Nov 2024

 Led the development of documentation portals, created cloud storage management systems, and worked on custom internal tools for customer management.

Full Stack Developer

Appetiser Apps

9

Melbourne, Australia

2021 - Dec 2023

- Built backend APIs, headless CMS solutions, and web applications using React.js and Vue.js.
- Deployed and maintained applications on AWS with CI/CD, contributing to in-house development templates and feature scoping.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in **Information Technology**

2018 - 2022

Technological University of the Philippines

- Valedictorian
- Magna Cum Laude
- Grayhawk Awardee for Academic Excellence
- Outstanding Graduate

Full Stack Developer

MagisSolutions

0

Rizal, Philippines

2021 - 2021

- Designed mockups and developed responsive web applications using Laravel, Node.js, Vue.js, React.js, and Tailwind CSS.
- Deployed applications via Forge and Envoyer while documenting updates and translating requirements into technical tasks.